Loreto Bodrogi

Security Officer, Abila, Kronos

Professional Overview

I am a professional and qualified security officer with five years of experience on the ground. A diligent and responsible worker, I work well in both static and mobile work modes. It is my hope to secure challenging employment with a well-established and respected security employer.

Experience

GASTech - Kronos Security Officer 2013-Present

- Both mobile and static day and night surveillance operations
- Gate inspections of vehicles and personnel
- Investigate disturbances
- Apprehend or evict trespassers
- Monitor the integrity of property boundaries
- Contact operations center and direct personnel in the event of an emergency

RQS Security Security Guard 2008-2013

- Report on activities on a nightly basis.
- Completed multiple short-term security assignments for clients of RQS.

Armed Forces of Kronos 2006-2008

• Excellent self-defense skills.

Education

Abila Community College

Associates Degree – Basic Studies GPA 3.5 2008-2011